goldboro.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy policy

###  **Personal Data**

Your personal data that we require from you throughout our cooperation is safely stored in our electronic systems, it is treated CONFIDENTIAL, and it is protected by the Data Protection Act. It is Goldboro policy not to disclose client information to non-affiliated third parties except with the consent of the client or when required for legal or regulatory purposes. Personal Data may include but is not limited to name, DOB, email, address, bank details, financial situation, trading activity, transaction history account balance information.

###  **Access to Personal Data**

Goldboro may disclose any such information except as may be necessary in the course of effecting transactions and otherwise administering customer’s account(s) and then only subject to customary undertakings of confidentiality, or as required by law. Access to such information is restricted to persons who need to know that information to provide services to the customer or Goldboro. Goldboro maintains physical, electronic and procedural controls to safeguard such information. These controls are reasonably designed to: (i) ensure the security and confidentiality of the customer’s records and information; (ii) protect against any anticipated threats or hazards to the security or integrity of the customer’s records and information; and (iii) protect against unauthorized access to or use of customer’s records or information that could result in substantial harm or inconvenience to the customer.

###  **Marketing and Communication**

Goldboro may contact you by email at any time to provide you with information on market trends, and/ or to inform you on marketing materials, training, and education or to enquire evaluation of its services. You may opt out from this application at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link situated at the end each email sent to you.
